[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From 1950-1953, Butterfly McQueen appeared in the TV sitcom Beulah. Which Academy Award winner played the title role?", "correct_answer": "Hattie McDaniels", "incorrect_answers": ["Ethel Waters", "Amanda Randolph", "Louise Beavers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Jack Ingram perform a song on the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words is not a term referring to sparkling wine?", "correct_answer": "All of these refer to sparkling wine.", "incorrect_answers": ["cava", "spumante", "sekt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the group formed by frogs and amphibians?", "correct_answer": "Herps", "incorrect_answers": ["Drosophillia", "Mollusks", "Nematodes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Besides flour and milk, what is the third essential ingredient of the batter for pancakes in the UK?", "correct_answer": "Eggs", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemon", "Jam", "Sugar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Spider Mans main nemesis in Spider Man 2?", "correct_answer": "Doc Oc", "incorrect_answers": ["Venom", "The Sandman", "The Goblin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does antepenultimate mean?", "correct_answer": "second from last", "incorrect_answers": ["next to last", "last", "middle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the music fields Frenchman Francois Tourte is famous for what?", "correct_answer": "He standardized the size of the violin bow.", "incorrect_answers": ["He invented the saxophone in collaboration with Adolphe Sax.", "He won the first Gorbachov International Music Award", "He was one of the first prominent saxophonists of the 19th century."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal has the broadest visual color spectrum?", "correct_answer": "Butterfly", "incorrect_answers": ["Elephant", "American Kestrel Falcon", "Bumblebee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the loch, allegedly inhabited by the notorious Loch Ness Monster?", "correct_answer": "Northern Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Wales", "Southern Ireland", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these movies did not star the actress who portrays Olive in Little Miss Sunshine?", "correct_answer": "The Sixth Sense", "incorrect_answers": ["The Family Plan", "Signs", "Raising Helen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these objects did the astronauts from Apollo 11 leave on the Moon surface during their mission?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Two drawings of the Western and Eastern Hemispheres of the Earth", "The signature of the American president, and their own signatures", "An American flag"]}]